Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 8 and District 8 Locals, 1936-1957 UE.4.1.8
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 8 Locals, 2.
  - Local 150F
    - Local 150F Finances, November 17 - December 1, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 189)
      - Lillian Rosenberg to Robert Logsdon, November 17, 1953; 1.
      - Logsdon to James Matles, November 23, 1953; 2.
      - Secretary of Matles to Logsdon, December 1, 1953; 3.
    - Local 150F Strike, May 29 - June 1, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 190)
      - Lillian Rosenberg to G.O. McMahill, May 29, 1951; 1.
      - McMahill to Rosenberg, June 1, 1951; 2.
    - Local 150F Officer Resignations, January 5, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 191)
      - Donald Abington, January 5, 1956; 1.
      - Henry Schnell, January 5, 1956; 2.
    - Local 150F Correspondence, Robert Logsdon to James Matles Regarding Facitonalism, March 19, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 192)
  - Local 156F
    - Local 156F Officers Lists, November 1949 - March 15, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 193)
    - Local 156F Incoming Correspondence, October 3, 1952 - February 17, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 194)
      - Julius Emspak to Max Kingsbury Regarding Strikes, October 3, 1952; 1.
      - Emspak to Kingsbury Regarding Strikes, October 6, 1952; 2.
      - Emspak to Kingsbury Regarding Strikes, October 10, 1952; 3.
      - Emspak to Kingsbury Regarding Strikes, October 17, 1952; 4.
      - Emspak to Kingsbury Regarding Strikes, October 24, 1952; 5.
      - Emspak to Kingsbury Regarding Strikes, October 31, 1952; 6.
      - Emspak to Kingsbury Regarding Strikes, November 7, 1952; 7.
      - Emspak to Kingsbury Regarding Strikes, November 13, 1952; 8.
      - Emspak to Kingsbury Regarding Strikes, November 21, 1952; 9.
      - Emspak to Alice Westbrook Regarding Per Capita and Finances, December 22, 1953; 10.
      - Emspak to Kingsbury Regarding Bonding, February 17, 1954; 11.
    - Local 156F Charter Supplies, November 1, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Local 157F
    - Local 157F Officers Lists, November 1, 1949 - December 6, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 196)
    - Local 157F Incoming Correspondence, September 27, 1950 - April 13, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 197)
      - Julius Emspak to Lee Allman Regarding Finances, September 27, 1950; 1.
      - Emspak to Carl Skinner Regarding Finances and Contract, April 2, 1951; 2.
      - Emspak to Thomas Sawyer Regarding Finances, April 14, 1951; 3.
      - Emspak to Sawyer Regarding Per Capita, August 11, 1953; 4.
      - Emspak to Raymond Walker Regarding Bonding, February 17, 1954; 5.
      - Emspak to George Stiglish Regarding Per Capita and Finances, April 13, 1955; 6.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Allman Regarding Finances, November 14, 1950; 7.
      - Fitzgerald to Sam Morelli Regarding Dues and Constitution, November 14, 1950; 8.
      - Fitzgerald to Morelli Regarding Officers and Negotiations, November 21, 1950; 9.
      - Secretary of James Matles to Local 157F Executive Board Regarding Organization, September 11, 1951; 10.
      - Matles to John Doubet Regarding Strikes and Caterpillar, October 1, 1951; 11.
    - Local 157F Outgoing Correspondence, December 2, 1949 - August 7, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 198)
      - Charles Allaman to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, December 2, 1949; 1.
      - C. Allaman to Emspak Regarding Supplies and Officers, December 19, 1949; 2.
      - C. Allaman to Emspak Regarding Finances, August 10, 1950; 3.
      - C. Allaman to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Finances and Inter-union Rivalry, October 3, 1950; 4.
      - C. Allaman to Fitzgerald Regarding Finances and Negotiations, November 8, 1950; 5.
      - Pauline Allaman to Fitzgerald Regarding Staff Finances, December 30, 1950; 6.
      - John Doubet to James Matles Regarding Inter-union Rivalry and Caterpillar, September 1951; 7.
      - Sam Morelli to Fitzgerald Regarding Factionalism, November 8, 1950; 8.
      - Morelli to Ray Klausner Regarding Officers, November 13, 1950; 9.
      - Morelli to Fitzgerald Regarding Officers and Dues, November 17, 1950; 10.
      - Tom Sawyer to UE Regarding Per Capita and Arbitration, August 7, 1953; 11.
      - Carl Skinner to Emspak Regarding Per Capita, February 1, 1951; 12.
    - Local 157F Per Capita Reports, October 1949 - May 1955 (Box 6, Folder 199)
    - Local 157F Proposed Budget, Expenses and Bills, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 200)
    - Local 157F Charter Supplies, November 1, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 201)
    - Local 157F Leaflets, November 28, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 202)
      - "Canton Harvester Workers Support Honest Unionism", November 28, 1950; 1.
      - Membership Drive, Undated; 2.
      - Policy Committee Card, Undated; 3.
    - Local 157F Policy Committee Resolutions, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 203)
      - Inter-union Rivalry with CIO, 1950; 1.
      - Negotiations, 1950; 2.
      - United Mine Workers Strike, 1950; 3.
    - Local 157F United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, February 8, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 204)
      - James Matles Memo, February 8, 1950; 1.
      - Petition, 1950; 2.
      - Local 157F Executive Board Letter to Sir, 1950; 3.
    - Local 157F Officers Election, November 21 - December 4, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 205)
      - Memo, 1950; 1.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to John Watkins, November 21, 1950; 2.
      - Ballot Results, December 4, 1950; 3.
    - Local 157F Canton Daily Ledger, January 27 - February 3, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 206)
      - Elvis Swan to Albert Fitzgerald, January 27, 1955; 1.
      - Fitzgerald to Swan, Febraury 3, 1955; 2.
      - Fitzgerald to James Murphy, February 3, 1955; 3.
    - Local 157F Correspondence, October 31, 1949 - August 11, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 207)
      - General Executive Board Statement Regarding CIO, October 31, 1949; 1.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Don Harris Regarding Staff Finances with December 30, 1950, Pauline Allaman Letter to Fitzgerald, January 4, 1951; 2.
      - Elvis Swan Report Excerpt Regarding Per Capita, July 10, 1951; 3.
      - Julius Emspak to Harris Regarding Per Capita, August 11, 1953; 4.
      - Swan Report Excerpt Regarding Speed-up and Strikes, Undated; 5.
  - Local 191F
    - Local 191F Officers Lists, January 23, 1950 - January 5, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 208)
    - Local 191F Mailing List with John Watkins Letter to Tom Wright, December 8, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 209)
    - Local 191F Incoming Correspondence, October 23, 1952 - December 28, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 210)
      - Julius Emspak to Jerome McFall Regarding National Strike Fund, October 23, 1952; 1.
      - Emspak to Arthur Styx Regarding Staff Finances, November 3, 1955; 2.
      - Albert Fitzgerald to Styx Regarding Staff Finances, December 28, 1955; 3.
      - Don Harris to Styx Regarding Staff Finances, December 13, 1955; 4.
    - Local 191F Outgoing Correspondence, Arthur Styx to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, December 1955 (Box 6, Folder 211)
    - Local 191F Charter Supplies, November 1, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 212)
    - Local 191F Correspondence, December 28, 1955 - January 1956 (Box 6, Folder 213)
      - James Matles to Wilford Krumm Regarding Staff Memos, December 28, 1955; 1.
      - Memo Regarding Per Capita and Officers, January 1956; 2.
  - Local 206F
    - Local 206F Per Capita and Charter Supplies, October - November 1, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Local 209F
    - Local 209F Officers Lists, November 1, 1949 - December 2, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Local 209F Membership List, January 1950 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Local 209F Incoming Correspondence, January 26, 1950 - Apirl 27, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Julius Emspak to Carl Kammeyer Regarding Dues, January 26, 1950; 1.
      - Emspak to A.J. Rousar Regarding National Strike Fund, October 23, 1952; 2.
      - Emspak to Clarence Baker Regarding National Strike Fund, December 18, 1952; 3.
      - Emspak to Eugene Strum Regarding Finances and Negotiations, April 27, 1952; 4.
    - Local 209F Outgoing Correspondence, April 14, 1953 - August 10, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - W.P. Brever to UE Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, August 10, 1955; 1.
      - Eugene Strum to UE Regarding Finances and Negotiations, April 14, 1953; 2.
      - Strum to UE Regarding Finances and Negotiations, May 22, 1953; 3.
    - Local 209F Charter Supplies and Financial Report, November 1949, March 1953 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Local 209F Loan, April 20 - 24, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Julius Emspak to Don Harris with April 14, 1953, Eugene Strum Letter to UE, April 20, 1953; 1.
      - Robert Logsdon to Emspak, April 24, 1953; 2.
    - Local 209F Correspondence, Robert Logsdon to James Matles Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, April 26, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Local 218F
    - Local 218F Officers Lists, April 27, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Local 218F Incoming Correspondence, January 26, 1950 - September 4, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Julius Emspak to Guy Fadalo Regarding Dues, January 26, 1950; 1.
      - Emspak to UE Locals Regarding Strikes and Danlstrom Metallic Door Strike, August 22, 1951; 2.
      - Emspak to Raymond Scritchfield Regarding Strikes, September 4, 1951; 3.
    - Local 218F Outgoing Correspondence, April 6 - October 17, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Tony Diccolo to UE Regarding Strikes, October 17, 1951; 1.
      - Raymond Scritchfield to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Negotiations with April 9, 1951, Fitzgerald Letters to Don Harris and Charles Hobbie, April 6, 1951; 2.
    - Local 218F Charter Supplies, November 1, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Local 218F Strike, October 17 - November 2, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Julius Emspak to Don Harris, October 22, 1951; 1.
      - Ton Piccolo to UE, October 17, 1951; 2.
      - Memo, November 2, 1951; 3.
  - Local 222F
    - Local 222F Officers Lists, November 1, 1949 - May 3, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Local 222F Membership List, January 7, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Local 222F Incoming Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Dorothy Bierschenk Regarding Supplies, April 18, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Local 222F Outgoing Correspondence, April 11 - May 9, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Dorothy Bierschenk to UE Regarding Officers, April 11, 1950; 1.
      - Ann Katcher to Julius Emspak Regarding Officers, May 9, 1950; 2.
    - Local 222F Per Capita Report and Charter Supplies, October - November 1, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Local 228F
    - Local 228F Officers Lists, November 1, 1949 - December 26, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Local 228F Incoming Correspondence, January 26, 1950 - January 22, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Julius Emspak to Homer McElroy Regarding Dues, January 26, 1950; 1.
      - Emspak to Clarene Moore Regarding Per Capita, January 22, 1951; 2.
    - Local 228F Outgoing Correspondence, January 15 - May 4, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Clarence Moore to Julius Emspak Regarding Per Capita, January 15, 1951; 1.
      - Moore to UE Regarding Unemployment and Plant Sale, May 4, 1951; 2.
    - Local 228F Notices of Delinquency and Suspension, May 1951 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Local 228F Charter Supplies, November 1, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Local 228F Plant Sale, May - August 6, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Charles Hobbie to James Matles, May 1951; 1.
      - Matles to Don Harris, May 7, 1951; 2.
      - Harris to Julius Emspak, Undated; 3.
      - Harris to Emma Meagher, August 6, 1951; 4.
  - Local 233F
    - Local 233F Officers Lists, December 28, 1948 - May 8, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Local 233F Membership List, November 20, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Local 233F Incoming Correspondence, October 23, 1952 - April 13, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - Julius Emspak to R.B. Pickett Regarding National Strike Fund, October 23, 1952; 1.
      - Emspak to Pickett Regarding Per Capita, April 13, 1955; 2.
    - Local 233F Outgoing Correspondence, Helen Martin to Julius Emspak Regarding Supplies, October 11, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Local 233F Charter Supplies and Per Capita, November 1, 1949 - May 17, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Local 233F Correspondence, Elvis Swan to Janet Regarding Officers and Locals 157F and 233F, February 5, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Local 235F
    - Local 235F Charter Supplies, November 1, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Local 249F
    - Local 249F Officers Lists, November 1, 1949 - April 15, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Local 249F Charter Supplies and Daryl Ratzlaff Letter to UE, November 1, 1949 - February 6, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Local 249F Correspondence, William Sentner to Grant Oakes Regarding Per Capita with December 2, 1949, Ray Spatt Letter to Maurice Young, December 5, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Local 271F
    - Local 271F Correspondence, Julius Emspak to Lucinda Kramer, January 4, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 35)